HEY, I JUST GOT MY, UH...
TEACHER EVALUATIONS.
CHECK OUT WHAT
THIS ONE STUDENT WROTE.
"I LOVED DR. GELLER'S CLASS.
MIND-BLOWING LECTURES.
"DR. GELLER, YOU ARE DEFINITELY
THE 'HOTTIE'
OF THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT."
AH, "HOTTIES OF THE PALEONTOLOGY
DEPARTMENT."
THERE'S A BIG SELLING CALENDAR,
HUH?
WHO WROTE IT?
OH, I WISH I KNEW
BUT THE EVALUATIONS
ARE ALL ANONYMOUS.
DO YOU STILL HAVE
THEIR FINAL EXAMS?
YEAH.
OH. 'CAUSE YOU COULD JUST MATCH
THE EVALUATION TO THE EXAM
WITH THE SAME HANDWRITING
AND, BOOM
THERE'S YOUR ADMIRER.
A HOT GIRL'S AT STAKE
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE'S RAIN MAN.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY ARE WE SO SURE
THAT THIS IS A GIRL?
IT'S A GIRL.
ANYWAY, IT WOULDN'T MATTER,
OKAY?
BECAUSE I'M A TEACHER,
SHE'S A STUDENT.
OH, IS THAT AGAINST
THE RULES?
NO, BUT IT IS FROWNED UPON.
I SEE.
BESIDES, THERE'S
A BIG AGE DIFFERENCE.
WELL, THINK OF IT
LIKE THIS
WHEN YOU'RE 90...
I KNOW. WHEN I'M 90,
SHE'LL BE, LIKE, 80
AND IT WON'T SEEM LIKE SUCH
A BIG DIFFERENCE.
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS
GOING TO SAY AT ALL.
NO. WHAT I WAS
GOING
TO SAY IS WHEN
YOU'RE 90 YOU'LL
STILL HAVE THE MEMORY
OF WHAT IT WAS
LIKE TO BE
WITH A 20-YEAR-OLD.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, CHANDLER,
YOU KNOW THAT GIRL
YOU WENT TO COLLEGE WITH
WHO BECAME A MOVIE DIRECTOR?
OH, YEAH, DANA KEYSTONE.
SHE WAS IN MY MOVEMENT CLASS.
WHAT'S A MOVEMENT CLASS?
IT'S CHANDLER'S WAY
OF PRETENDING
HE DIDN'T TAKE MIME.
WELL, LISTEN, ANYWAY,
SHE'S DIRECTING
THE NEW AL PACINO MOVIE.
YOU GOT TO GET ME AN AUDITION.
I HAVEN'T TALKED
TO HER IN TEN YEARS.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE, PLEASE, CHANDLER?
I WOULD OWE YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DO OWE ME SO MUCH.
YOU OWE ME $3,400...
DUDE, WHY ARE YOU
CHANGING THE SUBJECT?
WILL YOU MAKE
THE CALL OR WHAT?
OKAY, I'LL TRY.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
NOW, LISTEN
THE LAST DAY OF AUDITIONS IS
THURSDAY, OKAY?
SO I GOT TO GET IN THERE
BY THURSDAY, OKAY?
JUST REMEMBER THURSDAY.
THURSDAY.
CAN YOU REMEMBER THURSDAY?
YEAH, SO, TUESDAY?
THURSDAY.
LOOK, IF YOU NEED
HELP REMEMBERING
JUST THINK OF IT
LIKE THIS:
THE THIRD DAY, ALL RIGHT?
MONDAY, ONE DAY.
TUESDAY, TWO DAY.
WEDNESDAY, WHEN? HUH?
WHAT DAY?
THURSDAY!
THE THIRD DAY, OKAY?
THANK YOU.
OKAY. GOOD.
HEY, MON, I'M GOING
TO CHECK MY MESSAGES.
YOU JUST THOUGHT
OF THAT IN THERE?
SURE. YOU KNOW,
NATURE CALLED.
SHE WANTED TO SEE
WHO ELSE DID.
HELLO?
UH, RACHEL.
YOU GUYS, SOMEONE IS
IN OUR APARTMENT.
CALL THE COPS!
YOU'RE ON THE PHONE!
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD. THANK YOU.
THAT WAS THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
THERE WAS A FIRE AT OUR PLACE!
OH, MY GOD!
HOW BAD WAS IT?
WELL, HE DIDN'T SAY,
BUT IT WAS A FIRE.
I'M GUESSING
NOT VERY GOOD.
COME ON.
WE GOT TO GO.
YEAH, COME ON.
WHAT ARE YOU
SMILING ABOUT?
WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
THE PART I WANT
TO AUDITION FOR
IS A FIREMAN.
THIS IS SO MEANT TO BE!
WOW!
LOOKS LIKE YOU WERE
VERY GENEROUS
WITH YOUR GRADES
THIS SEMESTER.
( chuckles )
PROFESSOR GELLER?
YEAH?
I WANTED TO SAY
HOW MUCH I ENJOYED
YOUR CLASS.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
OW.
UM, I'M A LITTLE EMBARRASSED
ABOUT CALLING YOU
A HOTTIE ON MY
EVALUATION.
THAT WAS YOU?
YEAH.
I FELT A LITTLE WEIRD ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE A TEACHER.
I'M A STUDENT
BUT WOULD YOU
MAYBE WANT TO GO OUT
WITH ME SOMETIME?
OH, I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD BE
THE BEST IDEA.
OH, 'CAUSE I WAS THINKING...
THE SEMESTER IS OVER.
YOU'RE NOT MY TEACHER ANYMORE.
WHAT TIME?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET IT.
I SEE YOU
ALREADY GAVE ME AN "A."
GOTCHA.
I'M KIDDING! GOD!
OH.
SO, SERIOUSLY,
WHAT TIME?
Phoebe:
COMING THROUGH.
OH! COMING THROUGH.
OH, HELLO.
HI.
NO. RIGHT.
COMING THROUGH.
OKAY, WELL,
IT'S NOT SO BAD.
YEAH, MOST OF THE DAMAGE
IS PRETTY MUCH CONTAINED
TO THE BEDROOMS.
OH!
HEY, BUDDY
YOU THINK I COULD BORROW
YOUR UNIFORM THIS THURSDAY?
EXCUSE ME?
JOEY, HE'S WORKING.
YOU WOULD LOOK
GOOD IN THAT.
HOW BAD IS IT?
OH, IT'S BAD.
IT'S REALLY BAD.
THE ONLY THING THERE
THAT ISN'T BURNED IS AN AX
WHICH I DO NOT
REMEMBER BUYING.
HOW'S YOUR ROOM, RACH?
EVERYTHING'S RUINED:
MY BED, MY CLOTHES.
LOOK AT MY FAVORITE
BLUE SWEATER.
ISN'T THAT MINE?
FINE. I'M SORRY
FOR YOUR LOSS.
SO, UH, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE
TO LIVE HERE FOR A WHILE.
YOU LADIES
HAVE A PLACE TO STAY?
OH, WOW. OKAY.
LOOK, PAL, I AM
NOT IN THE MOOD
TO BE HIT ON
RIGHT NOW.
BUT IF YOU GIVE
ME YOUR NUMBER
I WILL CALL YOU
SOME OTHER TIME.
YES. THEY CAN
STAY WITH US.
HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT
WHAT STARTED
THE FIRE, MR. FIREMAN?
WELL, UH, DO EITHER OF YOU
SMOKE?
NO, NOT USUALLY
BUT, YEAH, I COULD USE
ONE RIGHT NOW. THANKS.
NO, NO, NO. DO YOU LIGHT
CANDLES, BURN INCENSE?
YES, I DO ALL THE TIME.
I LOVE THEM!
OH, MY GOD. I DID IT.
IT'S ME, IT'S ME.
I BURNED DOWN THE HOUSE!
OKAY, PHOEBE, CALM DOWN.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO PLACE BLAME, OKAY?
I WARNED HER
ABOUT THOSE CANDLES.
GOD, IT'S GREAT
TO CATCH UP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LONG IT'S BEEN.
HEY, CHANDLER, IS THAT...?
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
GOOD FOR YOU.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
IS IT...?
OKAY, SO, YEAH, MAYBE
WE CAN GET TOGETHER, UM...
CAN YOU HOLD ON
FOR ONE SECOND, PLEASE?
WHAT?
WHEN YOU'RE OFF THE PHONE,
YOU WANT TO GET A PIZZA?
HI, I'M BACK.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
OKAY, WELL, WE'LL DO IT THEN.
OKAY, BYE.
( gasps )
HEY, LISTEN, SO
WHEN'S MY AUDITION?
I MEAN, I KNOW
IT'S THURSDAY
BUT WHAT TIME?
HEY.
HI.
WE DIDN'T GET
TO THE AUDITION.
I'LL TAKE HER TO COFFEE
AND THEN WE'LL DO IT THEN.
WOW. SO, NOW YOU'RE GOING
ON A DATE WITH THIS GIRL?
HONEY, IT IS
NOT A DATE.
I HAVEN'T TALKED
TO HER IN TEN YEARS.
YOU CAN'T CALL UP
SOMEBODY
YOU HAVEN'T TALKED
TO IN TEN YEARS
AND ASK THEM FOR A FAVOR.
THERE ARE RULES.
YOU GOT TO PUT
IN SOME TIME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT LIKE, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE GOING OUT
WITH AN EX-GIRLFRIEND.
NO, WE ONLY
WENT OUT ONCE.
YOU DATED HER?!
NOT ONCE.
GREAT. WELL, WHY DON'T I JUST GO
OUT WITH AN EX-BOYFRIEND
AND, YOU KNOW, DO JOEY A FAVOR?
HEY, YOU WANT
TO DO JOEY A FAVOR?
MAYBE YOU GO OUT
WITH JOEY.
( gasps )
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
MY FRIEND JOEY'S
IN THE MOVIE BUSINESS.
MM, YOU KNOW WHO I RAN
INTO FROM SCHOOL?
HOWIE.
MY FRIEND'S NAME IS JOEY.
APPARENTLY, HOWIE'S EDITING NOW.
YEAH. HE CALLS ME UP AND ASKS ME
IF HE CAN EDIT MY NEW MOVIE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T
SPOKEN TO HIM
IN WHAT, TEN YEARS, AND
HE ASKS ME FOR A FAVOR?
YEAH, I'VE
ALWAYS HATED THAT HOWIE.
NO, NO "HOW YOU DOING?"
MAN, I MEAN, NOT EVEN
A CUP OF COFFEE FIRST.
THE NERVE, HUH?
YEAH.
REFILL?
NOW THIS IS LAST MINUTE
SO I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE MESS, OKAY?
WHO CARES?
OH, MY GOD.
SURE DIDN'T LOOK
THIS WAY
WHEN I LIVED HERE.
I KNOW!
NOW, LOOK
THERE'S ONLY ONE PROBLEM.
THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR ONE
SO I GUESS ONE OF YOU WILL
HAVE TO STAY AT JOEY'S.
WELL, SINCE THE FIRE WAS
KIND OF MY FAULT
I GUESS YOU SHOULD GET
TO STAY HERE.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
NOW, THIS WAS
NO ONE'S FAULT,
PHEEBS, OKAY?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
IT WAS MY FAULT,
SO YOU SHOULD GET
THE NICE ROOM.
OKAY!
WOO-WOO!
RACH, YOU'RE
THE FIRST GUEST
AT HOTEL MONICA.
HOTEL MONICA!
JUST TELL ME HOW
YOU LIKE YOUR EGGS
IN THE MORNING.
I THOUGHT I WOULD BRING THEM
TO YOU, YOU KNOW, IN BED.
WELL, YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH SO MUCH.
I HAVE.
THIS RIGHT HERE IS
WHERE I KEEP THE PIZZA
AND, UH, THAT'S WHERE
THE NAPKIN IS.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
I KNOW.
OH, PLEASE.
IT WAS SUCH A BIG CLASS.
YOU NEVER
EVEN NOTICED ME.
WHAT?
OF COURSE, I DID.
YOU, UH, YOU SAT
NEXT TO SLEEPY SLEEPERSON.
WHO?
OH, UH, I HAD TROUBLE
REMEMBERING
EVERYONE'S NAME
SO I KIND OF CAME
UP WITH NICKNAMES.
LIKE THE GUY ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF YOU WAS
UH, SMELLY VON BROWN SHIRT.
OH, YEAH.
SO, UH, DID YOU HAVE
A NICKNAME FOR ME?
OH, NO, NO.
YES, YOU DID.
WHAT WAS IT?
UM, IT'S CUTIE McPRETTY.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
LISTEN, I GOT
TO TELL YOU
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME.
YOU KNOW HOW
BEFORE YOU SAID
IT MIGHT BE WEIRD
THE WHOLE
STUDENT-TEACHER THING?
AND TO BE FRANK
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE,
TOO, BUT IT'S NOT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT AT ALL.
DR. GELLER!
BURT!
SO, DID YOU SLEEP
WELL LAST NIGHT?
I DID.
YEAH?
MONICA WAS SO SWEET.
SHE LEFT A LITTLE MINT
ON MY PILLOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT JOEY LEFT
ON MY PILLOW?
WHAT?
GUM.
WELL, WE DETERMINED
THE CAUSE OF THE FIRE.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT WAS MY CANDLE, MY CANDLE.
NO. THERE WAS AN APPLIANCE
LEFT ON IN THE BATHROOM.
IT LOOKS LIKE A CURLING IRON.
I DON'T USE A CURLING IRON.
WELL, SOMEONE DOES.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
MY HAIR'S STRAIGHT.
STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
COULD HAVE BEEN
A HAIR STRAIGHTENER.
OH.
THIS IS WHERE
I KEEP THE PIZZA
AND... HEY, WHERE'D
THE NAPKIN GO?
NOW, THERE YOU GO.
I WOULDN'T WANT MY BEST GUEST
TO STRAIN HER EYES.
THANKS, MONICA.
DOES THAT SMELL
BOTHER YOU?
THE SMELL FROM JOEY'S?
NO. I CAN HARDLY SMELL
IT OVER HERE.
OKAY.
WELL, YOU LET ME KNOW
IF YOU CAN.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, I CAN BAKE
A PIE TO COVER IT.
I CAN SMELL IT A LITTLE.
BAKE THE PIE.
OKAY.
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
OH, YES.
ONE MINUTE, PLEASE.
IT'S FOR YOU.
IT'S THE FIRE INSPECTOR.
OH.
HELLO.
YEAH, THIS IS PHOEBE.
REALLY?
( slightly disguising voice):
YEAH.
SO, IT TURNS OUT
THAT IT WASN'T THE HAIR
STRAIGHTENER
THAT STARTED THE FIRE.
NO, NO.
IT WAS THE CANDLES.
YEAH.
IT'S VERY NOT GOOD
LEAVING CANDLES UNATTENDED.
IN FACT, ONE OF
THE FIRST THINGS
THEY TEACH YOU
IN FIRE SCHOOL
IS, UH...
UH, OKAY.
WELL, I HAVE TO GO NOW.
WE HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME.
SHE'S INCREDIBLE.
I THOUGHT THE AGE DIFFERENCE
MIGHT BE A PROBLEM
BUT IT WASN'T.
IT WASN'T AT ALL.
ELIZABETH IS VERY MATURE
FOR HER AGE.
A CONCEPT LOST
ON SOME PEOPLE.
SO, IT'S OKAY TO
DATE A STUDENT?
WELL, NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, TECHNICALLY
IT'S NOT AGAINST THE RULES
OR ANYTHING
BUT IT IS FROWNED UPON.
ESPECIALLY BY
THAT PROFESSOR
WE RAN INTO LAST NIGHT--
JUDGEY VON
HOLIER-THAN-THOU.
WELL, ROSS, YOU JUST BE CAREFUL,
OKAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
A REPUTATION
AS, YOU KNOW, PROFESSOR
McNAILS-HIS-STUDENTS.
YEAH.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WELL, ROSS, IT SEEMS
PRETTY CLEAR.
WHAT'S
MORE IMPORTANT--
WHAT PEOPLE THINK
OR HOW YOU FEEL?
ROSS, YOU GOT
TO FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
JOEY, THAT IS SO SWEET.
HEY.
HEY, HEY, SO,
HOW'D IT GO WITH DANA?
ANY REASON I SHOULD LEAVE
A BLOCK OF TIME OPEN--
SAY, THURSDAY?
I COULDN'T DO IT.
YOU COULDN'T DO IT?
RELAX. I JUST NEED
MORE TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO
DINNER TONIGHT.
WHAT? YOU'RE GOING OUT
WITH HER AGAIN?
GOING OUT
WITH WHO?
UH, DANA KEYSTONE
FROM COLLEGE.
OH, YEAH.
WASN'T SHE...?
NO, THAT WAS DANA KAPLAN.
All:
OH, YEAH.
JOEY, YOU DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW HER.
AW, WHATEVER.
GREAT STORY AGAIN.
THE YARNS THAT
YOU WEAVE.
WHOO-HOO.
YOU KNOW, I SHOULD
GET GOING.
OH, NO, NO.
STAY, STAY, BECAUSE
YOU SHOULD...
YOU SHOULD STAY.
WOW.
OH, I AM
REALLY FLATTERED
BUT I JUST, I DON'T FEEL
THAT WAY ABOUT YOU.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT... NO, NO, NO.
I'M SORRY,
CHANDLER.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE
SUCH A SWEET GUY
AND I DON'T WANT
TO HURT YOU.
OH, I WISH THERE
WAS SOMETHING
I COULD DO TO MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
NO, NO...
REALLY?
OF COURSE.
WELL, IT JUST
HURTS SO BAD.
I, UH...
OH, I'M SORRY.
WELL, MAYBE THERE IS
ONE THING YOU CAN DO.
WHAT? ANYTHING.
ANYTHING.
WELL, I MEAN, THIS IS
JUST OFF THE TOP
OF MY HEAD NOW.
UM, BUT I HAVE
THIS FRIEND--
UH, THIS ACTOR FRIEND--
AND HE WOULD KILL ME IF HE
KNEW THAT I WAS DOING THIS.
UM, BUT, UM...
WOULD IT BE POSSIBLE
FOR HIM TO GET AN AUDITION
FOR YOUR MOVIE
SAY, ON THURSDAY?
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT YOU'D REALLY
FEEL BETTER
ABOUT ME REJECTING YOU
IF YOUR ACTOR FRIEND
CAN AUDITION FOR MY MOVIE?
THE HEART WANTS
WHAT IT WANTS.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
WELL, NOT MUCH HAS CHANGED
IN THE LAST FIVE MINUTES.
YES, IT HAS.
I MADE COOKIES.
I'M STILL FULL FROM
YOUR HOMEMADE POTATO CHIPS.
BUT YOU SHOULD
EAT THEM NOW
'CAUSE THEY'RE HOT
FROM THE OVEN.
OKAY.
OH, BUT NOT IN HERE.
YOU CAN'T EAT THEM
IN BED, REMEMBER?
NO CRUMBIES.
OKAY.
I'LL BE OUT IN A SECOND.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS DOESN'T LOCK,
DOES IT?
OH, JOEY, I'M SORRY.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO. BUT LOOK.
OH, THAT'S GOING
TO LEAVE A STAIN.
RACH, HEY,
IT'S FINE.
YOU'RE AT JOEY'S.
REALLY?
YEAH.
LOOK.
I'VE NEVER LIVED
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I KNOW.
WELL, DON'T WASTE IT.
IT'S STILL FOOD.
GEEZ.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO NOW, HUH?
YOU WANT TO GO GET
A DRINK?
UH, I CAN'T.
YOU HAVE
SOME STUDYING TO DO?
NO, I HAVE SOME
TURNING 21 TO DO.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER
WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE
WE USED TO...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
I'M JUST, I'M SO
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU.
DO YOU NOT WANT
TO BE SEEN WITH ME?
OF COURSE, I DO.
ARE THEY GONE?
UH, NO, THEY'RE STILL HERE
BUT I THINK
I'M ABOUT TO LEAVE.
WHAT?
NO, NO, WAIT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS STUPID.
WHO CARES WHAT
PEOPLE THINK?
I MEAN, WE LIKE
EACH OTHER, RIGHT?
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH THAT.
COME ON.
BURT.
LYDIA.
MEL.
THIS IS ELIZABETH.
HI.
AREN'T YOU IN MY
POPULAR CULTURE CLASS?
Ross:
THAT'S RIGHT, LYDIA.
ELIZABETH HERE
IS A STUDENT
AND, UH, WE'RE DATING.
AND YOU MAY
FROWN UPON THAT
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING
TO HIDE IT ANYMORE.
YOU ARE SO FIRED.
WHAT?
THEY'RE GOING TO FIRE YOU.
YOU CAN'T DATE A STUDENT.
IT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
REALLY?
IT'S NOT JUST
FROWNED UPON?
I LOVE IT AT JOEY'S.
HERE YOU GO.
NICE.
Rachel:
THANKS.
SO, YOU BUSY THURSDAY?
OH, VERY FUNNY.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU REMEMBER
BUT MY AUDITION WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE THURSDAY.
YOU GOT ME
THE AUDITION?
LET'S HUG IT OUT!
OKAY. OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO TO ME
IF YOU GET THE PART?
HEY.
LISTEN, UM...
YEAH, OKAY, I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
NOW, I KNOW THAT THEY SAID
THAT THE, UM,
THE HAIR STRAIGHTENER
STARTED THE FIRE
BUT I THINK
I'M PARTLY AT FAULT.
YOU SEE,
I DIDN'T TELL YOU
BUT, UM, BUT, UH...
I HAD RECENTLY
REFILLED THE TISSUES.
AND, SO, LET'S FACE IT,
THAT'S JUST KINDLING.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT'S BETTER
THAT I STAY AT JOEY'S.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
PHOEBE, THIS
WAS MY FAULT.
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW
WHAT, I'M FINE HERE.
OKAY.
CHANDLER, MONICA IS
LOOKING FOR YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH. SHE SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT CRUMBIES.
NO, NO, NO.
I WAS SO CAREFUL.
OKAY, YOU HAVE
TO SWITCH WITH ME.
MONICA IS
DRIVING ME CRAZY.
Joey:
THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL THE LADIES
WANT TO STAY AT JOEY'S.
NO, NO.
PHOEBE, I DON'T
WANT TO SWITCH.
PLEASE, COME ON.
I CAN THROW WET
PAPER TOWELS HERE.
NO, BUT AT MONICA'S,
YOU CAN EAT COOKIES
OVER THE SINK.
I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
SO MUCH FUN.
YEAH.
GOD, WHAT A MESS.
WOW. IT ACTUALLY IS
IN THE HANDBOOK.
I CAN'T DATE YOU OR HAVE
A HOT PLATE IN MY OFFICE.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE HAVE TO STOP
SEEING EACH OTHER.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH
I DID APPRECIATE YOU
STANDING UP FOR ME.
IT FELT REALLY NICE.
KIND OF MADE ME
LIKE YOU EVEN MORE.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I REALLY LIKE YOU, TOO.
BUT WE CAN'T DATE.
IT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
IT'S FORBIDDEN.
WOW.
WHAT?
JUST HEARING YOU
DESCRIBE IT
AS FORBIDDEN--
IT'S REALLY HOT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL... I-I DON'T CARE
HOW HOT IT IS--
IT'S.... IT'S WRONG.
STOP IT.
NO, NO.
IT'S WRONG.
IT'S-IT'S, IT'S NAUGHTY.
IT'S...
TABOO.
SHUT THE BOOK.
LET'S ALSO GET
A HOT PLATE.
SO?
SO...?
IT'S THURSDAY.
HOW WAS THE AUDITION?
MONDAY, ONE DAY...
TUESDAY, TWO DAY...
WEDNESDAY...
THURSDAY...
( gasps )
OH!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]